{"status":"Success","data":{"quiz_datas":[{"question_no":"233","question":"\u0d38\u0d4c\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d30\u0d02\u0d17 \u0d26\u0d48\u0d7c\u0d18\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a","option3":"\u0d28\u0d40\u0d32","option4":"\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d35\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"164","question":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d47\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d 0,6,24,60,120,210,_ ?","option1":"200","option2":"336","option3":"332","option4":"312","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"42","question":"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d23\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d42\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?","option1":"\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d21\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d39\u0d3f","option2":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d48","option3":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24","option4":"\u0d39\u0d48\u0d26\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"50","question":"\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d48\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b","option2":"\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d25\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d48\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b","option3":"\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d42\u0d38\u0d4d","option4":"\u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d48\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"596","question":"\u0d05\u0d1f\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d7b","option1":"\u0d30\u0d2c\u0d40\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d25\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d7c","option2":"\u0d06\u0d7c.\u0d15\u0d46. \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d7a","option3":"\u0d35\u0d3f.\u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d.\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7e","option4":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d46\u0d7b","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"382","question":"\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 :","option1":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d33","option2":"\u0d05\u0d16\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d20 \u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d24\u0d3f","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d26\u0d7c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7a","option4":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d36\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"204","question":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02 60 \u0d38\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d32\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d26\u0d42\u0d30\u0d02 20 \u0d38\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d09\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d33\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?","option1":"600 \u0d1a \u0d38\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d3f ","option2":"750 \u0d1a \u0d38\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d3f ","option3":"675 \u0d1a \u0d38\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d3f ","option4":"625 \u0d1a \u0d38\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d3f ","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"197","question":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2b\u0d46\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d17\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d30\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d09\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 ?","option1":"200","option2":"209","option3":"213","option4":"212","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"126","question":"\u0d28\u0d46\u0d39\u0d4d\u200c\u0d31\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d2b\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d02\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d35\u0d47\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d7d","option2":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d7d ","option3":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d7d ","option4":"\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d1f \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"43","question":"\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d, \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 - \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d08 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d ?","option1":"\u0d10\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d","option2":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d23 \u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41","option3":"\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f","option4":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d2b\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d","answer":"1"}]},"code":"100"}
